Maša Wu

+45 52600051 • info@masawudesign.dk • https://www.linkedin.com/in/masa-wu

QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY

- Technology Savvy: Proficient with Adobe software: Photoshop CC, Illustrator CC, Adobe XD, Premier Pro CC, After Effects, Animate CC and Dreamweaver CC. Competent in HTML, CSS, JS, SQL, JSON and MS Office suite.
- Effective Communicator: Competent in writing, editing, and proofreading business documents. Skilled in verbal communication and generating business and creative content.
- Storyteller: Experienced with writing storyboards with meaningful narrative curve. Communicating information and facts through engaging content that builds up a strong brand with loyal and active audience.
- **Team Worker:** Demonstrated working efficiently in an international team environment. Experienced being a SCRUM master, guiding a team of people by managing tasks progress, using problem-solving techniques and iterating.
- Self-Starter: Independent and self-confident, willing to take initiative when needed. Promote positive outlook on upcoming projects and persistent to accomplish set goals on time in a fast-paced environment.
- Detail Oriented: Meticulous about details and double-checking the work. Delivering high quality work while effectively prioritizing projects and deadlines
- Problem Solver: Resolving day-to-day administrative, operational and design problems at various working environments

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

Graphic and UX designer internship ◆ RATOONG, Copenhagen, Denmark

(3/2018-Present)

As a UX and graphic design intern my daily tasks consist of designing webpage and app mock ups using Adobe suite, clickable prototypes, performing various user testing, defining personas, writing customer journeys, wireframes. I am also responsible for writing design and UX documentation as well as creating marketing adds, creating catching banners and editing photos and videos for Facebook and Instagram ads.

Freelance Web Designer ♦ USA, Slovenia, Denmark

(09/2016-Present)

Worked pro-bono for multiple clients based in the USA and Slovenia. Projects ranged from a portfolio website for a professional graphic designer, a business website for my current employer and a food blog for my personal interest. Received top level feedback from clients.

- Created my food blog with WordPress.org http://www.misschili.net/
- Designed a portfolio website for a San Francisco based graphic designer client http://www.sallyhuang.net/
- Building professional business website for a restaurant in San Francisco http://www.misschili.net/rtb/rtb.html
- Built a personal portfolio showcasing my first semester projects: http://www.masawudesign.dk/kea/portfolio

Executive Assistant ♦ KLIMER STIRN & CO. d.n.o., Domzale, Slovenia

(11/2012-4/2018)

Klimer is a leading Slovenian company specialized in clean room testing for the pharmaceutical industry. In 2012, I got promoted and became an executive assistant. Now I am responsible for: managing business partners' and customers' relationship, preparing various regulation compliances prior to testing projects and post-processing test result, overviewing of company's logistics, reporting fleet expenses, planning business events, monitoring company's expenses, designing a strong logo and promotional material for Klimer brand.

- Communicating with local and international business partners
- Organizing meetings, planning international business trips, education seminars, and team building events
- Preparing business and design documentation

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Kea Multimedia Design & Communication (expected 07/2019) • KEA Københavns Erhvervsakademi, KØBENHAVN, DENMARK Office Administration Specialist Certificate (05/2017) • CITY COLLEGE OF SAN FRANCISCO, CA, USA

